BINAN BOOKSTORE USED BOOK RECYCLING
(濱南書店) (舊書回收)
Speaking of which,
對了
what will you do when I stop working at the start of the school year?
我暑假結束離職之後 老闆你打算怎麼辦
I'll hire someone new, I'm actually recruiting already.
我會雇新人 其實我已經在徵人了
So, the notice at the door is a job advertisement.
原來門口貼的就是徵人啟事啊
Yes, you will be the senior once the junior arrives.
沒錯 等新人進來後 你就要當前輩囉
Um, yeah.
嗯 是啊
What's up? You seem listless!
你的反應怎麼這麼沒勁啊
I'll leave the rest to you.
剩下就拜託你了
Okay.
遵命
Is "Kawashima Reiji" placed here?
《河島嶺二》放這裡對嗎
Ex-Excuse me.
不好意思...
Coming.
是
Why does this person seem familiar?
這個人怎麼有點似曾相識...
Are you Ichinose?
是一之瀨同學嗎
Do you need anything?
妳有什麼事嗎
I saw the job advertisement at the entrance.
我看到門口的徵人啟事
Oh.
喔
Huh? You're here for the job?
咦 妳是來應徵的嗎
Is that okay?
沒問題嗎
(Isn't that too sinful?) The person you're talking about is Mina.
(罪孽太深重了吧？) 你說的是深那小妹妹
Do you know each other?
原來你認識她嗎
She's a regular customer of this shop.
她是我們的常客
I didn't expect her to apply for the job.
想不到她居然會來應徵
I'm such a lucky guy.
我真是太幸運了
This old man becomes young again when he's excited.
老闆一興奮起來就像個小朋友
Mina, you're hired.
深那小妹妹 妳被錄取了
Wait a minute. Isn't this too fast?
等等 這也太快了吧
Because I know what kind of person she is.
因為我很瞭解她的為人
Ex-Excuse me.
請問...
My wife would definitely be happy. Follow me, Mina.
我太太一定也會很高興的 深那小妹妹 妳跟我來
Never mind, this way I can resign without any worries.
算了 這樣我也能無所顧忌地離職了
You're Mina, right?
妳就是深那小妹妹對吧
But your fringe is a bit…
可是妳的瀏海有點...
Can you do something about it?
妳能不能整理一下呢
The boss lady is quite straightforward.
老闆娘講話還真直接啊
But I feel the same way.
雖然我也有同感
I'm very happy that you came.
妳願意來我是很高興啦
That's right. How about I give you a haircut?
對了 不然我幫妳修剪一下吧
Wait. Stop, boss lady!
老闆娘 妳先等等啊
It's you, I was just introducing the job content.
是你啊 我正好在說明打工內容呢
I see.
這樣啊
Even though I like to worry about others, this is too fast.
就算我再怎麼愛替人操心 這也太急了
Speaking of which, what should I do now?
話說回來 我到底該怎麼辦
If Ichinose and I only have work interactions, here should be…
如果一之瀨同學跟我 只有工作上的交集 那我就...
Hello, nice to meet you. My name is Sajo.
妳好 初次見面 我叫佐城
The boss told me that you like to read, right?
我聽老闆說妳非常喜歡閱讀
Y-Yes.
啊 是的
When you read, does your fringe get in the way?
妳看書時不會覺得瀏海很礙事嗎
How do you usually solve it?
妳平常都怎麼解決的呢
I-I usually…
我...平常都...
L-Like this.
像這樣...
This is the first time I've seen her face clearly.
這還是我第一次看清楚她的臉
Not bad. Then clip it up when you're working.
很好啊 那妳就把瀏海夾起來吧
Y-Yes.
啊 好的
I look forward to working with you.
那明天起就請妳多多指教了
BINAN BOOKSTORE
(濱南書店)
Good morning…
早安...
Talking to a bookstore junior doesn't require such formality, right?
我跟在書店打工的後輩說話 應該不用這麼恭敬吧
And we're in the same grade.
而且我們還同年級
Morning, Ichinose.
早啊 一之瀨同學
Good morning.
早安...
It's so soft.
聲音好小
Oh, um…
呃 那個...
You are Ichinose, who sits next to me,
妳是坐我旁邊的一之瀨同學
right? Although we haven't talked much, it's nice to meet you.
對吧？雖然我們沒說過幾次話 請多多指教囉
She responds so slowly. Can she really do the job?
回答也太慢了吧 她真的有辦法好好工作嗎
Sajo, you're here.
佐城你來啦
Good morning, boss. You're full of energy.
老闆早安 你精神很好耶
From today on, I'll leave Mina to you. Be a good senior.
今天起深那小妹妹 就拜託你這個前輩了
I'll try.
我盡力而為
Teach her everything but the hard work.
除了粗重的工作 其他你就多教教她吧
Don't you dare have any weird ideas.
你可千萬別動什麼歪腦筋啊
What are you talking about?
老闆你在說什麼啊
I'm just kidding.
我開玩笑的啦
Firstly, it's about your fringe.
首先是妳的瀏海
That's right, remember to pin them up when you're working.
沒錯 打工的時候記得夾起來
Let's go then.
那我們走吧
First, check yesterday's sales list and organize the bookshelves.
首先要一邊確認昨天的銷售清單 一邊整理書櫃
It's easy.
這很簡單
When you respond to me, you can just nod.
妳回答我的時候可以只點頭沒關係
But when you're responding to customers, make sure to speak up.
但是面對客人時 妳記得要好好回答喔
O-Okay!
好...好的
When you look at it this way, there's quite a bit to do.
這麼一看 要做的事其實還滿多的耶
Um…
那個…我
We need a small stool here.
這時候要放個小踏板
Maybe I should do it.
不然還是我來吧
I-I can handle this.
這點小事我可以的...
Are you hoping to fall and then I'll catch you?
妳希望不小心跌倒 然後被我接住嗎
I'm not hoping for that.
這就有點...我不希望...
Next, we have to serve the customers.
接下來就要接待客人了
The store is open now, and customers might come in at any time.
現在已經開店了 所以隨時都會有客人上門
No matter what, you should organize the bookshelf first, just like I showed you.
總之妳照我剛才教的 先去整理書櫃吧
Leave the books on the high shelves to me, and I will handle the customer service.
高處的書跟招呼客人就交給我
As for the cashier's job, you can just observe first.
收銀工作妳就先在旁邊觀摩吧
I still have to give you that.
妳還需要這個...
INTERN
(實習生)
Just put the rope through. That's it.
把繩子穿過去 戴起來
I should have let her do it herself.
我真該讓她自己戴的
It's quite distant.
真疏遠
Do you have any questions?
那妳有什麼疑問嗎
Um…
那個…
If there's nothing, it's fine.
沒有的話也沒關係
Are there any?
有嗎
No.
沒有
It's hard to get along, hey.
這人好難相處啊
I think I covered everything, the rest is getting used to it.
工作內容我大致都教完了 剩下就等妳慢慢適應了
Although you'll definitely discover it later.
雖然妳之後一定也會發現
But first, let me tell you that many customers only look and don't buy.
但我還是先跟妳說 只看不買的客人滿多的
You can start by checking out the buttons on the cash register.
妳先去看看收銀機有什麼按鍵吧
Okay.
好
So, you're buying.
這客人居然要買書
There are no Mishima Yukio works here, so the store is not worthy of the name.
這裡居然沒有三島由起夫的書 真是愧對二手書店之名
The masterpiece "Music," with its wonderful sexual descriptions,
美妙地描寫性愛的傑作《音樂》
transformed forbidden bedroom affairs into beautiful art.
把禁斷的房事變成優美的藝術
The store claims to be a used bookstore, but none of his works are available.
沒有他的著作還敢自稱二手書店
- What a disgrace! - What is this old man talking about?
-成何體統！ -這位大叔在說什麼啊
Hello.
您好
You want to buy these two books, right?
您要買這兩本書對吧
Though I have no idea what you're talking about,
雖然我完全不知道你在說什麼
I know you have brought the goods to the cash register.
但我知道你把商品拿到了收銀台
Do you need a book cover?
請問您需要書套嗎
Yes, please.
那就麻煩你了
Okay.
好
The total for the two books is 220 yen.
兩本書一共220日圓
JAPANESE LITERARY MASTER
(日本文豪)
Thank you for your patronage.
謝謝光臨
You can always handle that kind of customer if you don't show your flaws.
對付那種客人時 只要不露出破綻總有辦法解決的
Ichinose…?
一之瀨同學...？
Let's go to the warehouse first.
我們先進去一下吧
Excuse me, I want to find the boss lady.
不好意思 我想找老闆娘
What's the matter?
怎麼了嗎
Because there was a weird customer,
因為剛剛遇到了古怪的客人
Ichinose cried.
一之瀨同學就哭了
What? She cried?
深那小妹妹哭了？
I let her rest in the warehouse, so don't go looking for her, boss.
我叫她去庫房休息了 但是老闆你別過去
I think this situation is better handled by a woman.
這時候還是讓女性來處理比較好
Okay, I got it.
好 我知道了
Thanks.
謝謝
After I resign, can Ichinose manage on her own?
我離職之後 一之瀨同學一個人沒問題嗎
And forget about serving customers,
別說是招呼客人了
she even struggles to communicate with her colleagues.
她就連跟同事交流都有困難了
Maybe I should talk to the boss, he might have some good ideas.
不然還是找老闆談談吧 說不定他會有什麼好主意
Uh… boss.
那個...老闆
In terms of the work here,
這裡的工作
customer service skills are essential, right?
就某方面來說 需要具備一些接待客人的技能吧
Yes, that's right.
嗯 沒錯
If so, I don't think Ichinose is suitable for this job.
我覺得一之瀨同學不太適合這份工作
What? How can you judge a book by its cover?
什麼 你怎麼能以貌取人
So, boss, are you going to clean up her mess?
那老闆你要替她收拾殘局嗎
And if you volunteer to take on tasks that Ichinose is unable to handle,
如果一之瀨同學做不來的事 老闆你全攬在自己身上
the boss lady will be unable to sit still.
老闆娘可不會坐視不管
I'm sorry.
不好意思
Ichinose has irritated me in an unexpected way.
沒想到一之瀨同學竟然讓我如此煩躁
Is it because we don't get along, or because I am too narrow-minded?
是因為我跟她合不來嗎 還是單純就是我心胸狹窄呢
Mina is…
深那小妹妹她...
She is the cutest regular customer at this shop.
她是這家店最可愛的常客
Where has your usual spirit gone, Grampy?
老闆 你平常不是很理性的嗎
I need to think of a solution.
我得想想辦法
At school, she's always alone.
在學校裡她總是孤零零一個人
But at least the shop owner cares about her in this second-hand bookstore.
但至少這家二手書店 還有個會在乎她的老爺爺
This should be her sanctuary, right?
這裡應該就是她的容身之處吧
Well… I'll go talk to her.
那...我先去找她談談好了
R-Really?
真的嗎...
Mm… But please don't expect too much.
嗯 但請你別抱太大期望
Alright, I got it.
好 我知道了
I can't let Ichinose hate this place.
我絕不能讓一之瀨同學討厭這個地方
Even if it's for the sake of the shop owner.
就算是為了老闆也好
So, only I, the person who is about to quit, can say these words, right?
那只能由我這個快離職的人來開口了
Sometimes women need to be tough too.
女人有時候也要強硬一點
Thank you, boss lady.
老闆娘 謝謝妳
You're welcome.
不客氣
I was just teaching her to prepare her mind for work.
我剛在教她工作前的準備心態
Leave the rest to me.
剩下的就交給我吧
Boss lady, were you just sorting out the accounts?
老闆娘 妳剛才是不是在整理帳簿？
Yes, that's right.
對對對
See you later then.
那我先走了
Ichinose, would you like to hear what I have to say?
一之瀨同學 我有話想跟妳說
The customer just now was weird, right?
剛才那個客人很奇怪對吧
No one can serve customers perfectly from the start.
沒有人一開始就能順利接待客人
It is normal for you to be scared to tears.
妳會害怕到哭也是很正常的
When dealing with such customers,
要對付那種客人
speaking casually can be extremely beneficial.
態度隨意一點會滿有效的
As long as they think you're unable to communicate, they'll shut up.
只要讓他們覺得妳很難溝通 他們就會閉嘴了
When you speak,
以妳來說
the other party may be scared if you give off a tough girl vibe.
如果妳表現出一點辣妹的態度 對方有可能就會退縮了
Serving customers is a tough job.
接待客人並不容易
There is no such thing as 100% right, but there is 100% wrong.
沒有百分百正確的答案 但卻有百分百的錯誤
No matter how unreasonable the other party appears to be,
無論對方有多不講理
we must deal with them properly as long as they are customers.
只要是客人 我們就必須正確應對
So I want to ask you, can you do that?
所以我想問妳 妳做得到嗎
Even if you are not good at talking,
就算平常不善言詞
you have to make people think you are "competent" when you are at work.
工作時也要展現出能幹的一面
Can you do it?
妳做得到嗎
If you can't, that means this job isn't for you.
不行的話代表妳不適合這份工作
-Just endure with the pocket money your parents gave you. -Idiot, calm down!
-妳就靠爸媽的零用錢忍耐一下 -笨蛋 我得冷靜
-There's no need to force yourself. -As her senior,
-妳沒必要勉強自己 -我身為前輩該做的
-What are you here for? -I shouldn't take away her right to choose,
-硬著頭皮來打工 -不該是剝奪她的選擇權
but rather allow her to make her own!
而是該讓她自行抉擇
Sorry. I just have one last question for you.
抱歉...我想問妳最後一個問題
Can you tell me whether you want to serve customers well?
妳能告訴我 妳真的有心接待客人嗎
I still think she should quit this job, to be honest.
老實說我覺得她應該放棄這份工作
If Ichinose visits as a customer,
以客人的身分光臨
the shop owner will greet her warmly.
老闆就會親切地招呼她
Isn't that better for them?
這樣對他們兩個來說應該才最好吧
I don't want to.
我不要...
I don't want to. I don't want to give up!
我不要... 我不想放棄
Why?
為什麼
I-I will try hard!
我會努力的...
Please don't fire me!
請不要辭退我
Wait! Lift your head up! Seriously!
呃 妳快把頭抬起來 我說真的
I-I'm just a part-time worker!
我不過就是個打工仔而已
I don't have the authority to fire you!
我才沒有權利辭退妳啊
(Dreaming Boy is a Realist, The)
《滿懷美夢的少年是現實主義者》
I will try to become competent!
我會努力變得精明能幹的
I got it! So lift your head up already!
我知道了 妳快把頭抬起來
What happened?
發生什麼事了
-Boss, Ichinose decided to stay. -What?
-老闆 一之瀨同學決定留下了 -什麼
So, start working hard tomorrow, okay?
那妳明天開始努力吧 好嗎
Is that so?
這樣啊...
It's about time, you guys can clock out now.
時間也差不多了 你們今天就先下班吧
No, there should still be work left. I want to stay.
不對 我的工作還沒做完 我要留下來
Alright, no need. But remember to come tomorrow.
不用啦 你明天也記得來上班就好
I got it.
我知道了
Then…let's go back, Ichinose.
那我們走吧 一之瀨同學
Y-Yes!
啊 好的
I'm a terrible person.
我真是差勁...
Ichinose, what's wrong with you? You seem so down.
一之瀨 你怎麼無精打采的？
Sorry for that.
說來慚愧
I haven't been getting along well with my sister recently.
最近我跟我妹相處得不是很融洽
MINA, NO REPLY
(深那 未回應)
Don't worry, okay?
沒事的啦 放心
Yuri.
小由梨
SAJO IS IGNORING US -WORKING? -YEAH
(小佐城不理人) (-打工嗎 -嗯)
Oh no.
糟了
2 USERS ARE ON A VIDEO CALL
(2人正在視訊通話)
Why do they want to video call?
為什麼要視訊通話
Here! You must want to go too.
我好想去這間店哦
The interior design is so fashionable.
店裡設計好時尚
Right? We are going to take a lot of photos.
對吧 我們一起去大拍特拍吧
If not, there will be so many things to do after school starts.
不然開學後又要忙東忙西的了
I'm okay with it. But have you done your homework for the summer?
我是無所謂啦 但妳的暑假作業寫完了嗎
I have been taking my participation in club activities very seriously.
我有很認真參與社團活動哦
I knew it. We will go to that shop as a reward for finishing your homework.
我就知道妳沒寫 那間店就當成妳寫完作業的獎賞吧
I will teach you the parts you don't understand.
作業有不懂的地方我會教妳
Aika, I love you!
小愛 我真的愛死妳了
Don't say that.
妳喔...
I FELL ASLEEP AS SOON AS I GOT BACK FROM WORK Girls need calories
(我打完工回來就睡翻了) 總覺得我們當女生的...
from time to time, right?
偶爾也得攝取點熱量吧
Yes, it feels like this shop should have low-fat options.
對啊 感覺這間店應該有低脂產品吧
Are you listening?
妳有在聽我說話嗎
But I'll definitely add the toppings.
但我絕對要加配料
Oh, Sajo really went to work.
啊 小佐城果然是去打工了
I-I see.
喔…是喔...
I sent him a hurry-up message, and it shows he read it.
我傳訊息叫他快點加入 他就已讀了
Huh? W-Wait.
什麼 等等啊
Sajo. We haven't talked for a long time!
小佐城 我們好久沒聊天了耶
Yes. So Natsukawa doesn't turn on the camera.
對啊... 原來夏川沒開視訊啊
You look very tired, don't you?
你是不是很累啊
I have a lot of troubles.
我也是有很多煩心事的
Really? Tell us.
是嗎 你快說來聽聽啊
Well… I have something to ask you.
那...有件事我想討教一下
Today at the place where I work, I made a girl kneel down…
今天打工的時候 我不小心讓一個女生跟我下跪了
That's too much, isn't it?
罪孽太深重了吧？
Well, just pretend you didn't hear it.
呃 妳們就當作沒這回事吧...
-No way! -I can't do it!
-不行 -休想
What did you do?
你做了什麼啊
Well… she is an introverted person.
這個嘛...她是個內向的人
You could say it is a tragedy caused by my disregard for her personality.
應該說這場悲劇是因為 我沒考慮到她的個性而造成的
In short, it's all your fault?
總而言之都是你的錯？
How shall I put it?
這...該怎麼說呢
Tell us.
你就說嘛
This is how it is.
是這樣的...
Anyway, this is my current worry.
總之這就是我目前的煩惱
To be precise, I don't know how to face tomorrow.
我不知道明天該怎麼面對
Tomorrow, will she still go to the bookstore?
明天她還會去打工嗎...
I bet she won't.
我投不會一票
Just kill me!
妳乾脆殺了我吧
Sajo, you need to cheer up!
小佐城你打起精神來啊
This is not entirely your fault.
這也不全是你的錯
After all, if she could communicate normally,
真要說起來 要是她能跟別人正常交流
this would not have happened, would it?
事情也不會演變成這個地步了吧
You are just a senior who wants to cheer her on, right?
你只是作為打工的前輩激勵她而已
Well…it should be, I guess.
嗯...應該是吧
There is a reason why you did this.
你會那麼做也是情有可原的
I got it!
我知道了啦
Sorry. My family called me to take a bath.
抱歉 我家人叫我去洗澡了
Goodbye!
再見囉
That's too sudden!
她也走得太突然了吧
Huh? Just now, were you cheering for me?
呃 莫非妳剛剛是在鼓勵我嗎
W-Why would you think so?
你...怎麼會這麼覺得
Because it doesn't sound like an objective opinion.
因為聽起來不太像是客觀意見...
It's your illusion!
是你的錯覺啦
S-Sorry.
對…對不起
By the way, how have you been doing recently, Natsukawa?
對了 夏川妳最近過得好嗎
Which aspect are you asking?
你是指哪方面
We have not seen each other since summer vacation, have we?
畢竟暑假後我們就有段時間沒碰面了
Now that you bring it up, you are right.
你這麼一說好像也是
But as long as you are having fun with Ashida, it's good.
不過看妳跟蘆田過得很開心就好
By the way, why don't you turn on the camera?
話說回來 妳為什麼不開視訊啊
Because I just finished bath.
因為我剛洗完澡
Huh? Ah, sorry.
啊 對不起
Speaking of, about the thing just now…
關於剛才那件事...
You have to listen to your junior's troubles.
你可要好好傾聽後輩的煩惱喔
I got it, thanks.
我知道了 謝啦
Good morning.
早安...
Morning, Ichinose.
早啊 一之瀨同學
Y-Yes! Good morning!
你好 早安
Well… I am really sorry about yesterday.
昨天...真的很抱歉
Hmm, hmm.
啊…嗯...
There's still time before the shop opens, let's tidy up slowly.
距離開店還有一段時間 我們慢慢整理吧
O-Okay!
好...好的
Your reply is more energetic than yesterday.
她的回答比昨天更有精神了
Does she have a compelling reason?
難道她有什麼非打工不可的理由嗎
It's time to open the shop. I'll flip the sign.
開店時間到了 我去把門牌翻過來
Let me do it.
讓我來吧
Well, I'll leave it to you.
那就拜託妳了
I-I'm done.
我翻好了
You're doing great!
妳做得很好
Such a big dust.
好多灰塵啊
That was close. Sometimes I treat her like a child.
好險 她有時候真的很像小朋友耶
Welcome.
歡迎光臨
I-I'll serve the customer.
我...我去招呼客人
A customer who checks out without saying a word?
結帳時一言不發的客人...
For Ichinose, it might be a bit difficult.
對她來說可能難度有點高
W-Welcome.
歡...歡迎光臨
T-This book is 130 yen.
這本書...是130日圓
I-I received your 500 yen.
收...收您500日圓
Uh… here is your change of 370 yen.
呃...找您370日圓
Um…
那個...
Hello!
您好 這個大小的書本
Do you need a book cover for a book this size?
我們可以幫您套上書套 請問有需要嗎
Thank you for your patronage!
謝謝光臨
What's wrong with you, Ichinose? You are different today.
一之瀨同學妳怎麼了 妳跟昨天完全判若兩人啊
Amazing! What did you do?
太厲害了 妳怎麼辦到的
I watched some videos about how to serve customers.
我看了一些接待客人的影片...
You're so sensible! Keep serving customers in this state!
太令人佩服了 妳就繼續保持這個感覺接待客人吧
O-Okay.
好...好的
Um… I'll go tidy up the bookshelves inside.
那個...我先去整理後面的書櫃
Based on her performance today, she clearly does not want to give up.
她今天的表現 看起來是真的不想放棄這份工作
Even though it is not my place to ask about her personal life,
雖然我不好過問別人的家事
I am really interested in why she had to do it.
但還是很好奇她非打工不可的理由
Sajo, Mina, it's about time to take a break.
佐城 深那小妹妹 差不多該休息囉
Okay.
好
The only chance to chat
我能跟一之瀨同學閒話家常的時間
with Ichinose would be now, right?
大概就只有現在了吧
Ichinose, you're here today too.
一之瀨同學 妳今天還真的來了耶
What am I saying? It sounds like I'm nitpicking.
我在說什麼啊 聽起來超像在找碴的
Because I had a reason to do it.
因為我無論如何都不能放棄...
So, why did you want to take this job?
是說妳為什麼會想來打工呢
Because I want to "be self-reliant".
因為我想自力更生
Huh? What? That's too excellent.
什麼 這也太優秀了吧
I've never considered such a thing.
我從沒想過這種事
But isn't it too early? We are only in our first year of high school, right?
不過會不會有點太早了啊 我們才高一耶
I want to stop depending on my brother.
我想擺脫對我哥的依賴...
So, you have a brother.
原來妳有哥哥啊
He's a senior student council member.
他是高三的風紀委員
A boy from the student council member?
風紀委員的男生？
Is it that senior who looks like a bear?
是那個像熊一樣的學長嗎
You are completely different from him, including your appearance.
兄妹長得也太不像了吧 從頭到腳包括體型也不像
But why? A little sister's reliance on her brother is not a problem.
為什麼呢 妹妹依賴哥哥沒什麼不妥吧
Do you wish to depend but can't?
是妳想依賴也依賴不了嗎
Speaking of which, this is already about her family affairs.
等等 這已經算是她的家事了吧
We probably aren't close enough to talk about things this deeply.
我跟她還沒熟到可以聊得這麼深入
Let's just leave it at that for now.
暫且就問到這吧
I… love my brother the most.
我...很喜歡我哥哥
When reading at home, I was always…
我在家裡看書的時候總是...
sitting on my brother's lap,
會坐在哥哥的腿上
leaning against his stomach.
靠著他的肚子閱讀
It's warm and comfortable.
又溫暖又舒適
What's that? It sounds super comfortable.
這是怎樣 太療癒了吧
But one day, my brother brought a woman home.
可是某天哥哥帶了一個女生回家
Since then, I have spent less time talking with my brother.
在那之後 我跟哥哥說話的時間也越來越少
-Even so, I still want to be with my brother. -Huh? Can I listen to this?
-但我還是想跟哥哥在一起 -這些話我適合聽嗎
-One day, I decided to express -You shouldn't be telling me this!
-某天我決定把這份心情 -這些內容不該跟我說的吧
-these feelings to my brother. -Wait! I have a bad feeling!
-告訴哥哥... -等等 我有種不祥的預感
I don't want to listen… but I really want to.
我不想聽 但又好想知道
I noticed a pair of shoes I did not recognize when I got home from school.
我放學回家後看見一雙沒看過的鞋子
I instantly realized they were Senior Yuri's shoes.
我立刻意識到那是由梨學姐的鞋子
But my mind was blank at that moment.
但當時我腦中一片空白
I dashed to my brother's room and opened his door without knocking.
我不假思索地奔向哥哥房間 沒敲門就推開了房門
And then…
結果...
And then…?
結果...？
And then I saw…
我就看見...
Se-Senior Yuri being pinned down by my brother.
由梨學姐被壓在哥哥身體下方...
They were kissing…!
他們在接吻...